hostkarle.in 2018-09-30

# Privacy Policy - Hostkarle Web Hosting Company

## **Privacy Policy**

### Privacy Policy - Hostkarle

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.hostkarle.in (the “Hostkarle”).

### WHEN DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, Use Live Chat, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site. Provide us with feedback on our products or services

### PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

\- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, debitcard, paypal, net banking, paytm), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information. 

### USE OF SERVICES, WEBSITE VISITS AND SUPPORT

Data relating to your online activity on our websites with respect to our Services, including the following:

* IP address
* browser type and version
* geographic location
* pages you view

how you got to our Services and any links you click on to leave our Services when you update your information, communicate with us, or order new Services metadata about your use and your contacts’ use of our Services and your emails you send (including clicks and opens)

your interactions with any videos we offer issues you encounter requiring our support or assistance any device or other method of communication you use to interact with the Services

We store this data we collect in a variety of places within our infrastructure, including system log files, back end databases and analytics systems. 

Your telephone conversations with us (which we may monitor or record).

### SOCIAL MEDIA

Information from third party social networking sites, including information that social networking sites provide to us if you use your credentials at such social networking sites to log into some of our Services (such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign-up form).

The information you allow us to access varies by social networking site, and depends on the level of privacy settings you have in place at the social networking site. You can control and find out more about these privacy settings at the applicable social networking site.

### OTHER SOURCES

* Information you provide to us at seminars or to our partners;
* Information you provide to us in surveys;
* Information that is publicly available; and
* Information you consent to us receiving from third parties.

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We have a legitimate interest in running a successful and efficient business and in providing you with Services and useful content, and we use the information we collect, both on its own and combined with any other information we collect about you, for the following purposes:

* To provide the requested Services to you;
* To provide you with useful content;
* To ensure the proper functioning of our Services
* To offer and improve our Services;
* To provide you with requested information or technical support
* To facilitate your movement through our websites or your use of our Services;
* To do a better job of advertising and marketing our Services (our use of your information to do this is performed with your consent where required by applicable law);
* To advertise and market third party products and services (such advertisement is only performed with your permission where your consent is required by applicable law)
* To diagnose problems with our servers or our Services;
* In connection with our security and compliance programs;
* To administer our websites;
* To communicate with you;
* To target prospective customers with our products or services (such targeting is only performed with your permission where your consent is required by applicable law);
* To assist us in offering you a personalized experience or otherwise tailor our Services to you; and

As otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We also use the information we receive in aggregated and anonymized formats to produce reports on trends and statistics, such as mobile search trends, email open rates by industry, campaign best practices or the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, our websites or evaluated or purchased our products and services.

Payment information that you provide to us, including credit card data, will only be used to facilitate payment for our products and services.

We also use recorded telephone conversations for quality control purposes, to train our employees and for our own protection.

Hostkarle respects your privacy and takes its responsibilities regarding the security of your customer information very seriously. We are committed to providing you with a professional, valuable and personalized service whilst safeguarding your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to Hostkarle business. It has been created to explain to you the way in which Hostkarle use your personal data. This information will assist you to determine whether or not to provide us with your personal information.

This Privacy Policy applies without exception to all Hostkarle customers. It is applicable for personal data collected from persons located worldwide. We may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of all changes through our website at least one month prior to any change being implemented. This Privacy Policy explains the following regarding Hostkarle’ treatment of personal data:

### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

As further described below, We may share your personal information with::

* other members of the Hostkarle family
* our partners
* third party service providers and vendors
* in connection with a sale, merger, acquisition or corporate reorganization
* authorized users within your organization
* for legal reasons.
* If you sign up for our Services through a referral from a friend, we may share information with your referrer to let them know that you used their referral to sign up for our Services.

### **CHILDREN PRIVACY**

We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal data on our Website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Website is directed to persons under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access this Website at any time or in any manner.

We will take appropriate steps to delete any personal data of persons less than 13 years of age that has been collected on our Website without verified parental consent upon learning of the existence of such personal data.

### LEGAL PROCESS

Lastly, if legally required to do so, or if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary, we may disclose your personal information to courts of law, law enforcement authorities and other relevant third parties, such as internet service providers, to conduct an investigation, respond to a third party or law enforcement subpoena or court order, bring legal action, prevent harm to others or pursue other relief when you or a third party are or may be:

* violating our terms and conditions of use;
* causing injury or other harm to, or otherwise violating the property or other legal rights, of us, other users, or third parties; or violating federal, state, local, or other applicable law.

This disclosure can include transferring your information to the U.S. and other countries outside the European Economic Area. To the extent we are legally permitted to do so, it is our policy to notify you in the event that we are required to provide your personal information to third parties in connection with a subpoena.

### Definitions of personal data?

**Personal data is any information that allows you to be identified.** The types of personal data Hostkarle collect may include details of your name, address, telephone number, email address, fax number and date of birth.

We do not collect personal data about your racial and ethnic origin, political opinion, religious beliefs or other beliefs of a similar nature, membership of a trade union, physical or mental health or conditions, sexual life or any other sensitive information.

### Practices and procedures to collect your personal data

Hostkarle collect personal data from you through the use of enquiry and registration forms, direct personal contact with you and every time you e-mail us your details. We will use your personal data where it is necessary to do so because it is relevant to Hostkarle' dealings with you (i.e. it is relevant to the provision of the services that you have requested from Hostkarle) including for billing, customer service and network management.

Without your consent, we will not use your personal data for direct marketing, including the provision of offers for Hostkarle and its third party partners' products and services and customer surveys. We will not process personal information about you without your express consent. Hostkarle will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others.

Hostkarle may disclose your personal data to carefully selected business partners and third party suppliers to whom we engage to provide services. However, other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, Hostkarle will not disclose or share your personal data with any other third party without your express consent unless this is necessary to provide the services or products which you requested when providing us with your personal data or as required by law.

### Direct marketing

If you have consented at the point of collection to Hostkarle (and/or any third party) providing you with direct marketing material you will be requested to elect the type of media via which this material shall be provided (for example, by post, e-mail, telephone or fax). We will only provide you with such material via your chosen media.

If, at any stage, you object to Hostkarle' use of your personal data for direct marketing or to the media in which such material is being sent, you may choose to unsubscribe to its receipt. If you have consented to receive third party direct marketing you will need to unsubscribe directly with that third party.

### Use of "cookies"

Hostkarle may use "cookies" on our website and its sub-sites. A "cookie" is information that a web site puts on your hard drive so that it can remember pieces of information about you when you next visit the website or a related website. We use cookies to record personal data about you only when you use our web site in order to facilitate your future activities.

Unless otherwise notified by us, Hostkarle will not use personal data sent in a cookie for marketing purposes. If you prefer not to receive cookies from our site, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser.

### Security of your personal data

Hostkarle has in place appropriate technical and organizational security measures to prevent unauthorized or unlawful disclosure or access to or, accidental or unlawful loss of or destruction, or alteration or unauthorized disclosure of or access to, or other damage to your personal data. These measures ensure an appropriate level of security in relation to the risks inherent in the processing and the nature of the personal data to be protected.

### Your rights to your personal data

We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected. During this period, you may contact our officer at any time if you would like to see details of the personal data that we hold about you. You also may inform yourself about the purposes for which your personal data are being used, details of the parties with whom we may share your personal data or to ask us to correct, update, supplement or delete this personal data.

### Hostkarle enforcement of this Privacy Policy

If you have a question or enquiry about this Privacy Policy or a complaint about the way Hostkarle has used your personal data you should first contact our Data Protection Officer. The Hostkarle' Data Protection Officer is responsible to deal with and respond to all enquiries that come from any client. The Data Protection officer reports directly to the Company Executive Director. The Hostkarle' Executive Director meets on an "as necessary" basis to discuss our Privacy Policy and any individual complaints or disputes.

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

### DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

### DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine. The method we chose is at our sole discretion. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

* By email: support@hostkarle.com
* By visiting this page on our website: https://www.hostkarle.in/contact.php
